# OSMAN ÇAĞRI GENÇ

## SKILLS

My main language is Javascript since my 12 years old. So, I'm good in JS, VueJs, NodeJs. I love to develope websites, I'm good in HTML, CSS, PHP. Also, I developed with C#, C++, Python. I'm not best in there, I can say "I'm good."

| Javascript, VueJs, NodeJs, React | 5/5   |
|----------------------------------|-------|
| C#, C++, Python                  | 3.5/5 |

#### ABSTRACT

I'm a software engineer since 2017. I worked on C#, Desktop Applications until 2020. Now, I'm working on Javascript, Full Stack Developer. I am very good at developing algorithms and solving problems.

As a career plan, I would like to see myself as a backend-developer on remotely.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Software Developer | Aketroniks | May 2021 -

I'm developed with PHP, HTML, JS, CSS and VueJS. IoT monitoring project has frontend by VueJS and backend by NodeJs. I edited folder structure and coding. CMS Project has frontend by PHP, I added Codelaniter framework and edited coding.

#### Software Developer | Fembak | Apr 2020 – Apr 2021

I was a VueJs Developer in Online Shopping App and Ticketing Automation System. Also, I helped Laravel Backend and React-Native Projects.

## Software Developer | MOSAS | Sep 2017 – Jan 2020

I was a .Net Developer. In generally, I created some C# Windows Form and WPF Desktop Applications. Also, I developed embedded application with Qt C++ and basic scripts with Python.

Intern | TAI | Jul 2016 - Aug 2016

Intern | BTM | Jul 2015 - Aug 2015

# EDUCATION

2,92 | 2017 | Selcuk University, Computer Engineering





osmcgrgenc@g mail.com +905459077765





osmcgrgenc

osmcgrgenc

https://sazik.dev

# CHARACTERISTICS

I was a member of Selcuk Uni., IT
Community until degree from
university. Now I'm a member of
MUGET's Rover Team. I love to help
people and team works. I like to
share my knowledge. I like to take
care of stray animals and discover
new places.